Here we have a really fun style of skirt.
Sometimes it boarders on trendy, sometimes it doesn't, it just depends.
It's all how you reference it and how you design around it.
We have an asymmetric skirt, asymmetric meaning it's not the same length all around.
This one, I've chosen to depict one that is short in the front than it is in the back.
A easy way to render this, when you're drawing it, decide, of course, where you want your waistline, then decide how short or how long you want the front part of your skirt to be.
I want my front part of my skirt to be right there, well that's a little short.
I want the front part of my skirt to be right there and I want the back part, as I said earlier, to be longer.
The easiest way to do that and have it look three dimensional, is to dip it down behind the legs, from the corners.
That way, if you're looking at something straight on, you can see that it is longer in the back.